They'd never forget the day he drifted into town.
High Plains Drifter is a western, drama, mystery
film directed by Clint Eastwood.
A gunfighting stranger comes to the small settlement of Lago.
After gunning down three gunmen who tried to kill him, the townsfolk decide to
hire the Stranger to hold off three outlaws who are on their way.
The Stranger, played by Clint Eastwood.
Sarah Belding, played by Verna Bloom.
Callie Travers, played by Marianna Hill.
Dave Drake, played by Mitchell Ryan.
Morgan Allen, played by Jack Ging.
Mayor Jason Hobart, played by Stefan Gierasch.
High Plains Drifter is a 1973 American Western film directed by Clint Eastwood, written by Ernest
Tidyman, and produced by Robert Daley for The Malpaso Company and Universal Pictures.
The film stars Eastwood as a mysterious stranger who metes
out justice in a corrupt frontier mining town.
The film was influenced by the work of Eastwood's collaborators,
the film directors Sergio Leone and Don Siegel.
The film co-stars Verna Bloom, Mariana Hill, Mitchell
Ryan, Jack Ging and Stefan Gierasch.
The film was shot on location on the southern shores of Mono Lake, California.
Dee Barton wrote the film score.
The film was critically acclaimed at the time of its
initial release and remains popular.
The film explores themes of gunslinger, showdown, outlaw, gunfighter, guns.
The tone is emotional and mind_bending.